A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Projects (Grants), RG 3, Subgroup 1 and Subgroup 2 FA005
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (Grants), 1947-1996; 3; 750 Cubic Feet
  - Projects (Grants), 1947-1989; 1
    - National Legal Aid and Defender Association, 1975 March-April (Box 659, Folder 3951)
    - National Legal Aid and Defender Association, 1975 April (Box 659, Folder 3952)
    - National Legal Aid and Defender Association, 1975-1977 (Box 659, Folder 3953)
    - National Legal Aid and Defender Association Tax Information, 1973-1975 (Box 659, Folder 3954)
    - National Manpower Institute Formerly: Manpower Institute, The, 1972-1973 (Box 659, Folder 3955)
    - National Manpower Institute, 1973 June-September (Box 660, Folder 3956)
    - National Manpower Institute, 1973-1975 (Box 660, Folder 3957)
    - National Manpower Institute, 1973 March-November (Box 660, Folder 3958)
    - National Manpower Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 660, Folder 3959)
    - National Manpower Institute Tax Information, 1973 (Box 660, Folder 3960)
    - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., 1952-1970 (Box 660, Folder 3961)
    - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., 1972-1975 1978 (Box 661, Folder 3962)
    - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., Tax Information, 1970-1976 (Box 661, Folder 3963)
    - National Midcentury Committee for Children and Youth Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 661, Folder 3964)
      See Also: White House Conference on Children and Youth Cross - Reference card for Related files.
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc., 1971 April-August (Box 661, Folder 3965)
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc., 1971 August (Box 661, Folder 3966)
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 661, Folder 3967)
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc., 1972 July-December (Box 661, Folder 3968)
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc., 1973 March 6 (Box 662, Folder 3969)
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc., 1973 December (Box 662, Folder 3970)
    - (The) National Movement for the Student Vote, Inc. Tax Information, 1971 (Box 662, Folder 3971)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, 1947-1952 (Box 662, Folder 3972)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, 1952-1953 (Box 662, Folder 3973)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, 1953-1968 (Box 663, Folder 3974)
    - National Municipal League, 1948-1952 (Box 663, Folder 3975)
    - National Municipal League, 1952-1955 (Box 663, Folder 3976)
    - National Municipal League, 1955-1968 (Box 663, Folder 3977)
    - National Museum and Art Gallery - Gaborone Botswana Tax Information, 1974-1975 (Box 663, Folder 3978)
    - National Museum and Art Gallery - Gaborone Botswana, 1974-1976 (Box 663, Folder 3979)
    - National Park Foundation, Tax Information, 1970-1982 (Box 663, Folder 3980)
    - National Park Foundation, 1970-1975 (Box 664, Folder 3981)
    - National Park Foundation, 1975 July 31 (Box 664, Folder 3982)
    - National Park Foundation, 1977-1982 (Box 664, Folder 3983)
    - National Park Service, 1962-1982 (Box 664, Folder 3984)
    - National Planning Association, 1952-1954 (Box 664, Folder 3985)
    - National Planning Association, 1953-1955 (Box 665, Folder 3986)
    - National Planning Association, 1955 January-December (Box 665, Folder 3987)
    - National Planning Association, 1956-1958 (Box 665, Folder 3988)
    - National Planning Association, 1956-1958 (Box 665, Folder 3989)
    - National Planning Association, 1958-1969 (Box 665, Folder 3990)
    - National Planning Association, 1970-1974 (Box 666, Folder 3991)
    - National Planning Association - Inter-American Research Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 666, Folder 3992)
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1941-1959 (Box 666, Folder 3993)
      NRPA was formed 8/13/1965 by merger of: American Recreation Society, American Institute - of Park Executives, National Recreation Association, National Conference of State Parks, and American Association of Zoological Parks and Aquariums.
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1959-1963 (Box 666, Folder 3994)
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1963-1965 (Box 666, Folder 3995)
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1972-1973 (Box 666, Folder 3996)
    - National Recreation and Park Association Tax Information, 1973 (Box 666, Folder 3997)
    - National Recreation and Park Association - Street Life Project, 1973-1983 (Box 666, Folder 3998)
    - National Recreation and Park Association - Street Life Project, Tax Information, 1973-1983 (Box 666, Folder 3999)
    - National Repertory Theatre Foundation, The, 1961-1964 (Box 667, Folder 4000)
    - National Repertory Theatre Foundation, The, 1964 May-September (Box 667, Folder 4001)
    - National Repertory Theatre, The, 1964-1966 (Box 667, Folder 4002)
    - National Repertory Theatre, The, 1965-1966 (Box 667, Folder 4003)
    - National Repertory Theatre, The, 1966-1969 (Box 667, Folder 4004)
    - National Research Center of the Arts, Inc., 1972-1977 (Box 667, Folder 4005)
    - National Research Center of the Arts, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 668, Folder 4006)
    - National Research Center of the Arts, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 668, Folder 4007)
    - National Research Center of the Arts, Inc. Tax Information, 1977-1983 (Box 668, Folder 4008)
    - National Rural Center, 1975-1976 (Box 668, Folder 4009)
    - National Rural Center, 1976-1977 (Box 668, Folder 4010)
    - National Rural Center, 1977 May-June (Box 668, Folder 4011)
    - National Rural Center, 1977-1978 (Box 669, Folder 4012)
    - National Rural Center, 1978 March-October (Box 669, Folder 4013)
    - National Rural Center, 11/2/1978 (Box 669, Folder 4014)
    - National Rural Center, 11/2/1978 (Box 669, Folder 4015)
    - National Rural Center, 11/2/1978 (Box 669, Folder 4016)
    - National Rural Center, 1978 November-December (Box 669, Folder 4017)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 January 3-8 (Box 670, Folder 4018)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 January 9-15 (Box 670, Folder 4019)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 January-February (Box 670, Folder 4020)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 February-March (Box 670, Folder 4021)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 March-May (Box 670, Folder 4022)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 May-June (Box 670, Folder 4023)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 June (Box 671, Folder 4024)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 June-September (Box 671, Folder 4025)
    - National Rural Center, 1979 November-December (Box 671, Folder 4026)
    - National Rural Center, 1979-1980 (Box 671, Folder 4027)
    - National Rural Center, 1980 May-June (Box 671, Folder 4028)
    - National Rural Center, 1980 July-October (Box 671, Folder 4029)
    - National Rural Center, 1980 October-December (Box 672, Folder 4030)
    - National Rural Center, 1981 January-April (Box 672, Folder 4031)
    - National Rural Center, 1981 April-June (Box 672, Folder 4032)
    - National Rural Center, 1981 June-August (Box 672, Folder 4033)
    - National Rural Center, 1981 August-September (Box 672, Folder 4034)
    - National Rural Center, 1981-1982 (Box 672, Folder 4035)
    - National Rural Center, 1982 March-May (Box 673, Folder 4036)
    - National Rural Center, 1982 July (Box 673, Folder 4037)
    - National Rural Center, 1982 July-December (Box 673, Folder 4038)
    - National Rural Development Finance Corporation, 1978-1980 (Box 673, Folder 4039)
    - National Rural Development Finance Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 673, Folder 4040)
    - National Rural Development Finance Corporation, 1981-1983 (Box 673, Folder 4041)
    - National Rural Development Finance Corporation Tax Information, 1979-1983 (Box 673, Folder 4042)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1957-1964 (Box 674, Folder 4043)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1964-1966 (Box 674, Folder 4044)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1966-1969 (Box 674, Folder 4045)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1969-1971 (Box 674, Folder 4046)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1971-1972 (Box 674, Folder 4047)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1972-1976 (Box 674, Folder 4048)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1973-1975 (Box 675, Folder 4049)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1976 November-December (Box 675, Folder 4050)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1976-1978 (Box 675, Folder 4051)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1978-1979 (Box 675, Folder 4052)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1979 June-December (Box 675, Folder 4053)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1970 January-May (Box 675, Folder 4054)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1970 June-October (Box 676, Folder 4055)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1970-1971 (Box 676, Folder 4056)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1971 May-September (Box 676, Folder 4057)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1971-1972 (Box 676, Folder 4058)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1972-1973 (Box 676, Folder 4059)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1973-1974 (Box 677, Folder 4060)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1974 March-November (Box 677, Folder 4061)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, 1974-1975 (Box 677, Folder 4062)
    - (The) National Urban Coalition, Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 677, Folder 4063)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1941-1943 (Box 677, Folder 4064)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1944-1948 (Box 677, Folder 4065)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 677, Folder 4066)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 678, Folder 4067)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 678, Folder 4068)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1955 January-May (Box 678, Folder 4069)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1955 June-December (Box 678, Folder 4070)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 678, Folder 4071)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 678, Folder 4072)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1958 (Box 679, Folder 4073)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 679, Folder 4074)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 679, Folder 4075)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1961 May-October (Box 679, Folder 4076)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 679, Folder 4077)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 679, Folder 4078)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1963 March-December (Box 680, Folder 4079)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 680, Folder 4080)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1964 March-December (Box 680, Folder 4081)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1965 March-December (Box 680, Folder 4082)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1966 January-December (Box 680, Folder 4083)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1967 (Box 680, Folder 4084)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1968 January-June (Box 681, Folder 4085)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1968 July-October (Box 681, Folder 4086)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1968 October-December (Box 681, Folder 4087)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1969 January-February (Box 681, Folder 4088)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1969 March 6-13 (Box 681, Folder 4089)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1969 March 13-15 (Box 681, Folder 4090)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1969 June-August (Box 682, Folder 4091)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 682, Folder 4092)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1970 July-October (Box 682, Folder 4093)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 682, Folder 4094)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1971 May-July (Box 682, Folder 4095)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1971 September-December (Box 683, Folder 4096)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 683, Folder 4097)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1973 June-July (Box 683, Folder 4098)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1973 September (Box 683, Folder 4099)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1973 September-October (Box 683, Folder 4100)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1973 October-December (Box 684, Folder 4101)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1974 January-April (Box 684, Folder 4102)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1974 April-June (Box 684, Folder 4103)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1974 June-July (Box 684, Folder 4104)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1974 August (Box 684, Folder 4105)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 684, Folder 4106)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1975 February-July (Box 685, Folder 4107)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1975 July-December (Box 685, Folder 4108)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1976 February-June (Box 685, Folder 4109)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1976 June-September (Box 685, Folder 4110)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 685, Folder 4111)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1977 March-May (Box 686, Folder 4112)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 686, Folder 4113)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1978 March-September (Box 686, Folder 4114)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1978 September (Box 686, Folder 4115)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 686, Folder 4116)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1979 January 9 (Box 687, Folder 4117)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1979 January-April (Box 687, Folder 4118)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1979 April 4 (Box 687, Folder 4119)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 687, Folder 4120)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1980 September (Box 687, Folder 4121)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1980 September-November (Box 688, Folder 4122)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1980 December (Box 688, Folder 4123)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1981 March (Box 688, Folder 4124)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1981 July-December (Box 688, Folder 4125)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1981 December 9 (Box 688, Folder 4126)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1981 December (Box 688, Folder 4127)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1982 January-March (Box 689, Folder 4128)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 689, Folder 4129)
    - National Urban League, Inc., 1983 March-April (Box 689, Folder 4130)
    - National War Fund, 1943-1947 (Box 689, Folder 4131)
    - Native American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1971 (Box 689, Folder 4132)
    - Native American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1972 (Box 689, Folder 4133)
    - Native American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1973 (Box 690, Folder 4134)
    - Native American Legal Defense and Education Fund, Tax Information, 1970-1974 (Box 690, Folder 4135)
    - Native American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1974 March-July (Box 690, Folder 4136)
    - Native American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 690, Folder 4137)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 690, Folder 4138)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 690, Folder 4139)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 691, Folder 4140)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 691, Folder 4141)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1980 April-May (Box 691, Folder 4142)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1980 June-September (Box 691, Folder 4143)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981 February-May (Box 691, Folder 4144)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 691, Folder 4145)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981 May-July (Box 692, Folder 4146)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981 July-August (Box 692, Folder 4147)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981 September-October (Box 692, Folder 4148)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981 October-November (Box 692, Folder 4149)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981 November-December (Box 692, Folder 4150)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 693, Folder 4151)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 March (Box 693, Folder 4152)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 March 10-16 (Box 693, Folder 4153)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 March-April (Box 693, Folder 4154)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 May 3-5 (Box 693, Folder 4155)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 May 5-10 (Box 694, Folder 4156)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 May-June (Box 694, Folder 4157)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982 July-December (Box 694, Folder 4158)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 694, Folder 4159)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 694, Folder 4160)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1984 February 21 (Box 695, Folder 4161)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1984 February-March (Box 695, Folder 4162)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1984 May-August (Box 695, Folder 4163)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1984 August-December (Box 695, Folder 4164)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 695, Folder 4165)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 696, Folder 4166)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1968 February-March (Box 696, Folder 4167)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1975-1976 (Box 696, Folder 4168)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1976 March-August (Box 696, Folder 4169)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1977 (Box 696, Folder 4170)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1978 January-August (Box 696, Folder 4171)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1978-1984 (Box 697, Folder 4172)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1984-1985 (Box 697, Folder 4173)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1985 March-June (Box 697, Folder 4174)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1985-1986 (Box 697, Folder 4175)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1986 May-December (Box 697, Folder 4176)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - International Project, 1987 (Box 697, Folder 4177)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project (Formerly: Natural - Resources Defense Council - Project on Species & Rainforest Management), 1975 April-August (Box 698, Folder 4178)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1975 September (Box 698, Folder 4179)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1975 October-December (Box 698, Folder 4180)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1975-1976 (Box 699, Folder 4181)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1976 April-June (Box 699, Folder 4182)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1976 July-August (Box 699, Folder 4183)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1976 August-December (Box 699, Folder 4184)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Threatened Species Project, 1977-1986 (Box 699, Folder 4185)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1976 April-December (Box 700, Folder 4186)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1976-1977 (Box 700, Folder 4187)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1977 October-December (Box 700, Folder 4188)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1977-1978 (Box 700, Folder 4189)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1979 (Box 700, Folder 4190)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1980 February-March (Box 700, Folder 4191)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 9/11/1980 (Box 701, Folder 4192)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1980 February-November (Box 701, Folder 4193)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1981-1982 (Box 701, Folder 4194)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1982-1983 (Box 702, Folder 4195)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council - Urban Transportation Project, 1983 May-July (Box 702, Folder 4196)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1966-1974 (Box 702, Folder 4197)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1974-1975 (Box 702, Folder 4198)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1975 February-May (Box 702, Folder 4199)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1975-1976 (Box 702, Folder 4200)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1976-1977 (Box 703, Folder 4201)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1977-1979 (Box 703, Folder 4202)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1980-1982 (Box 703, Folder 4203)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1983 February-July (Box 703, Folder 4204)
    - (The) Nature Conservancy, 1983 July (Box 703, Folder 4205)
    - Near East College Association, Inc., 1946-1954 (Box 703, Folder 4206)
    - Near East College Association, Inc., 1954-1956 (Box 704, Folder 4207)
    - Near East Emergency Donations, Inc., 1967-1973 (Box 704, Folder 4208)
    - Near East Foundation, 1949-1966 (Box 704, Folder 4209)
    - Neighborhood Committee for the Asphalt Green, 1977-1979 (Box 704, Folder 4210)
    - Neighborhood Committee for the Asphalt Green, 1980-1981 (Box 704, Folder 4211)
    - Neighborhood Committee for the Asphalt Green, 1981-1982 (Box 704, Folder 4212)
    - Neighborhood Committee for the Asphalt Green, 1983 August (Box 705, Folder 4213)
    - Neighborhood Committee for the Asphalt Green Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 705, Folder 4214)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 705, Folder 4215)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc. Tax Information, 1974-1976 (Box 705, Folder 4216)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc., 1976 February-September (Box 705, Folder 4217)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 705, Folder 4218)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 705, Folder 4219)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services of Jamaica, Inc. Tax Information, 1982-1988 (Box 705, Folder 4220)
    - Neurosciences Research Foundation, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 706, Folder 4221)
    - Neurosciences Research Foundation, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 706, Folder 4222)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1971-1975 (Box 706, Folder 4223)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1975 February (Box 706, Folder 4224)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 706, Folder 4225)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1976 July-September (Box 706, Folder 4226)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 707, Folder 4227)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 707, Folder 4228)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1978 January-February (Box 707, Folder 4229)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1978 February-March (Box 707, Folder 4230)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1978 March-August (Box 707, Folder 4231)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1980 September 30 (Box 708, Folder 4232)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1978-1980 (Box 708, Folder 4233)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1980-1981 (Box 708, Folder 4234)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1981 March-September (Box 709, Folder 4235)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 709, Folder 4236)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 709, Folder 4237)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1983 May (Box 709, Folder 4238)
    - (The) New Alchemy Institute, 1983 June-October (Box 709, Folder 4239)